Now, thanks for your response. I think we
asked the questions about the the vendor
responses for the questions we sent. I
think you feel that that one has said
you'd be getting that to us by Friday
or something like that. Yeah, that's
that's my goal. I checked with our
influence that we did receive.
Similar questions already during like
when we contracted so I wanted to make
sure I need to point with them to make
sure I answered like how they answered.
So I mainly self or Friday to get you
to get back to you. Did you get the
pen test results? So I got that link. I
got the link, but then I realized you
can't. Just click on and you have to do
some type of NDA signing. Yes. So I'll
have to do that part, but I just want to
submit it all together. Yeah, like
instead of piece by piece. So I'll do
this correctly. So yeah, you should get
the pen test and I'll get the report out
to you. We probably have already provided
it to someone. Or to the
review, but I'll, I'll get you the latest
versions of the pen tests have been
updated document. Thanks, Sir. Yeah.
OK. Do you just accept this
and probably get started? OK?
It's like we mentioned earlier call,
we asked about the sizing. I'll
touch base with you offline about
that. Alright, cool. Great. Thank you.
Um, was it, was it, was it
Ryan? Ryan, you had the other questions
for Harris, possibly.
Did I have that right? Yeah, it was
right. I mean, we don't got to jump right
in here. I just wanted to make sure we
had the right people, that's all. Yeah,
yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah. We'll put, we'll
put it all on Harris when the time comes.
So. To Harris and
the cough yeah Harris is will assign it
to him don't all all kidding aside we
just came from a. DSM
inquiry working session and some of the
questions kind of led over to this this
side of the House. So we'll get to that
in just a minute. With this is an open
forum more or less. We were continuing
our discussion around rules, use cases,
set up the investigation, but I did have
some questions for you, Howard, I want to
save. With the very end, uh, I want
to make sure I capture them correctly.
It's my it's my responsibility to you and
the team making sure tracking where we
are. OK, sounds good. Thank you.
Appreciate it. Alright, so
like any other calls, um, I'll let's open
the first time for a minute for the
teams, different teams to ask their
question. I'll start with maybe chat. Do
you have anything for Proofpoint? You're
going to make me first?
Uh, no, But if you give
me a minute, I just have
to double check my docs, see
if there's any outstanding thing. OK,
So however, is the document that
Harris provided regarding our endpoint
agent and any sort of questions
regarding application, right?The thing
was, was that for you or that
was for another team to review? Do
you mean the table with the long
term storage options? No, this was
something about like our endpoint, the
appellate listing. Was Fernando and I
asking those questions? Yeah, basically.
In the rationale in case we have to go
to like an EDR solution or whatever that
we have to say, you need to whitelist
this and and you guys got those responses
that I sent over. I don't think, I think
you were still working on more in-depth
responses unless you just sent it to
Fernando because I didn't get it. I got
it. Got it, I got it. Harry sent it
to couple days ago, so Henry and Henry
had the the chance to look at it. But
thank you. I did see that e-mail I
haven't got I haven't gone in detail. So
I was waiting for Fernando to come so we
can review it together. Yeah, just let us
know. I know we provided that initial
response to add or Don whoever was just.
Talking, but we, we took back your more
inductive questions to the product team.
And so the, the response I sent over a
few days back was the updated response.
So let us know if you need any additional
clarity there. Well there I'll send those
if you have done so you can see how
are you Sir, could I have?Some of that
being tracks, but if there's more more
detail, it's good to know. I'll send it
to you as well. Thank you. For sure.
Thank you so much for the question now.
Or should we move to the next question? I
know somebody who asked the question. Go
for it, please. Ryan, you want to go
ahead. Now here
I am, yeah. So I've
been focused on labels for
the last year. And so
we're trying to migrate over
the label detection that we
have. And so
we tried, you know, doing dictionary
lists of goods and figured out
that we're not scanning metadata there.
So we made conditions and so.
In particular, we have
a credit card policy
that's looking for credit
cards with keywords and.
Excludes documents that are
properly labeled, restricted, or
critical. So
when I'm building my detector, I've
got my red score for the
credit cards, um. Greater than
0 and my keyword list
greater than 0 and then.
But I couldn't figure out
how to put in the
detector the condition of the
label for the metadata.
Yeah, I have condition may have been. So
yeah, I was just trying to figure out
how to get that in there. Sure. So
there's essentially two ways to do this,
right? You can, there should be already a
field that is classification labels
within the rule, right? And you're
talking about the MIP labels, right?
Yeah, yeah. So though that functionality
is already built into the tool. So
you should see that field sensitivity
labels within a rule, and you can
call those labels directly. Now,
initially you'll just see the observed
value. So if any documents have been
interacted with, you know, transferred
move. We'll start to pick up on those
labels, right?I I
heard you mentioned one thing, that
you you're not scanning the metadata
fields with a dictionary condition. That
is not entirely true. You can
add a metadata attribute to the
detector expression itself to scope the
detection to only occur on a
certain. Like content type or content
part. So you can use metadata for
e-mail. There's quite a few, right? You
can use subject line, you can use
e-mail body. But if you did go
to the dictionary route, you can
absolutely put in the you create the
dictionary with the names and you can.
Absolutely. Have it scanned just the
metadata?So Harris and maybe we can get
that set up right now like right under
you might change the screen and we can go
over the set up so we can get that out of
the way from this call. Would you mind
doing that?And then
we can get Harris to workers to do the
setup. And here's just one coming around
what you just mentioned, right? Like, you
know, we can always just see the observed
values, something like that. This is the
issue that I have with observed values,
right? It seems that we need to allow
some sort of effectuation before we can
actually tap into some. Sort of values,
right? Um. Not not necessarily, right.
You can still actually connect your
classification account and then you'll
see them. But yeah, by default it it,
it would force you to wait until we
see like a file activity with the labels
on it. But there is a, there is
a in the administration under
integrations, you'll see classification
accounts and you can connect your. Um,
you know you can connect your Microsoft
account there as well.
So there's a few different ways, but
you're right, yeah, if you're not
connecting the classification account
directly, it would wait until the
observed values were seen and then. So
if you're doing your account here, so
you'll need your Microsoft tenant ID and
account IDs, so the tenant. Ideas
provided by Microsoft and then
the account ID's are provided
by. Like within
that MIP unified labeling, you'll see,
and we could provide you like an
example if you're not sure what it
looks like. But yeah, you can connect
to Microsoft Account here and then you'll
see all of those labels and.
Yeah. I just wanted to show also Ryan,
that this might be good for the team to
know as well. We talked about it on the
e-mail side, but that also applies to end
point where you can call out specific
attributes in the detector expression and
for example, have it scan the metadata of
a file only, right, So. You can
also do that now for that might be
labels. We already have that integration
built in, so creating a dictionary and
going through that effort is not
necessary, but in the future if there
are. You know if there is
content that you want to specifically
scope scanning for to a file part, then
you have the ability to do that.
OK. So I'll, I'll get to the we'll,
we'll, we'll, we'll get to the tenant ID
stuff. I can pull that up here.
Um, but as if without using
classification. So the the way that
I was getting detections to work
and I built conditions for each
of the different labels. Now we
have 3 different environments and so
we have three different sets of.
Anyways, um, that I was trying to
add in there, so I wasn't sure
if we were doing partial matching and
so I put in goods for one.
I put in the label name, not
the display name and trying to match
on that, but you can see that
it is. There's doing some some
matching there. Yeah, Yep.
Um.
But so this is based on the observed
values I assume? Or did you put those
custom values in there? I tried both ways
and wasn't getting success with custom
values and so I actually did do.
I gathered all files and uploaded
them through endpoint to get them
to trigger here OK.
One of the things that we
noticed or that I noticed was
that I have these.
Sample MSG files right?
Our new label taxonomy
includes do not forward
and all TD staff
which are both e-mail
only labels. But if
I upload these files
it's not detecting.
The label content within those
MSG files.
So I wasn't sure if MSG was
not supported or.
And let me double check. Umm, we
have a zoom.
Yeah, give me just a moment. So
for cloud and endpoint, let's see.
Yeah, I actually don't see
that as a supportive file
type that MSG file. OK,
Yeah, OK. So we have
this use case though this
all TV staff labeled.
Um.
Is for internal emails only and
so we don't want people going
into their Outlook and and saving
out an e-mail because it's it's
not an encrypted label, saving out
an e-mail with altered staff label
on it and then uploading that
content. Elsewhere we wanted to block
that right? So if you can't
detect the label, then our next
phase was how do we go
about blocking all MSG files from
being uploaded?
You can create a rule, right? Um, let
me just make sure. You should be able
to create a rule based on that file
type. So you would just create a rule
saying like block all web file uploads of
this file type. Let me just make sure
make a rule or make a condition. And
then a rule, no, you wouldn't, you
wouldn't need the I mean, because it's
just going to be blocking just regardless
of what what's in there or what
MIP labels on it, right? It's just
based on that MSG extension, right?
Yes, because we could figure out a way
to read any other content of those file
types. Yeah, so you can create a rule
saying block if the protocol is on file
upload and the extension. So go to a
block rule actually instead of a
detection rule.
Yes, on the left hand side you'll
see Prevention Endpoint rules in that
menu. Yeah, under Endpoints.
Yep. So this is where you would create
like a prevention rule. And we don't have
to save it right now, but I'll just show
you what I mean here. So this is where
you would create a rule to basically
block prompt allow. So if you click on
new rule here and then just do create
rule. And you could just do
block uploads of MSG files or something
like that, yeah. And here
it would be pretty simple. Um, yeah, just
web file upload and then Yep, next. And
then you would just call the extension
here. So
add a row and then just select extension.
Under Files Resources.
Yeah, right here.
And then you can just add um dot
MSG. And
then add it as a new value.
So is this.
Is that only doing extreme last against
this? Then that's what it's looking for.
So this could be any type, right? It
doesn't necessarily need to be one that
you guys can crack and look into, right?
Uh, what do you mean, uh,
like, um, encrypted files or other
file formats that are unknown to
Proofpoint, but we use here at
D. So we
would be able to detect the file
type file extension, but yeah, they're
not supported for content scanning
specifically. Yeah, OK. Yeah. So if you
have files that TD is using that
proof point can't scan, and you don't
want those files to be uploaded, then
yeah, you can. Add them to this this
same rule.
You could just click on that
MSG and you could just add
to that list there. OK, just
type something up in here. So
yeah, so for example, like we
have Cade is a file type
that we have.
Exceptions or detections around um,
so if I wanted to
do an exception for this
type of file file, I
would need to make a
condition out of it first,
is that right?Exception. What
would you? So if this wasn't here
right, what would we need the exception
for exactly?
Different policy, uh,
past file password
protected policy. So
um. Were specifically looking
for. This is a key
pass database, so by default
the agent won't scan files
that are password protected or
encrypted. So are you asking
if I'm not sure if
I'm understanding the question exactly?
Yeah, so let me.
I would say we have this KBX file, you
know right now, you know we can't scan
it, right? And then you don't want it to
be uploaded. So you can add in here to
block any upload occurring. And you
mentioned an exception, right? So are you
saying you want only certain users to be
able to upload files like?DBX files.
Yeah. So we were finding
that it was this one
and the other one that
we encountered with labels was
um, message dot RP MSG,
right. So that's when we
use like the do not
forward label, it encrypts the
e-mail. And so that
if you were man in
the middling it you or
unauthorized recipient, you would get
a messages message dot RPMS
MSG file which requires authentication
in order to open it
up within Outlook and. So
yeah, we're trying to,
um. That there are some
people who who need to use those those
files and and be able to send that. So we
want to have this as an exception as
well. Yeah. So that's what you do is you
would create kind of this rule with the
file with this KDX file in here as a
block and then you would create an allow
rule which will. Basically supersede any
of the prompter block rules that will get
evaluated first. And you can say, all
right, if the protocol is an upload, if
the users are part of this group and
it is this extension, then you know,
basically allow it to go through. OK, OK,
so. Yeah, you see,
You see, sorry, Harris, on that one,
when you said told him to create
an allow rule, do you mean a
detection rule? No, sorry. So can you
click on that activity and Action tab
up there?Right
next to settings right here.
So we have, I know it's
a little confusing, it's called
prevention rule, but we do have
an action that will actually allow
users. So it's still technically a
prevention rule, but it's like stop
evaluating. This is basically the
sequencing. Agent Realm, you put it to
matters.
So just to comment there, you have to
be very careful when you just allow like
this is something here that was
implemented by proof point recently. We
only want to just allow when we actually
putting like a global rules, right?
Because allow will actually skip
everything. You just. You just putting a
a condition for for a one on file, it's
going to be everything that matches this
condition. So you have to be very
careful, right? One of the things that we
talk about internally is that we probably
want if we have a policy that is
triggering on specific file, we actually
go and create a condition that actually
allows that user. To bypass that policy
rather than having an allowed policy that
that would pass and everything. Yeah,
that works too. You can basically exclude
them directly from that prevention rule.
Exactly. Yeah. Yeah, you could do that
way as well. Yeah, I'm just.
Yeah, go ahead. Sorry, Harry, sorry. When
you say, when you say Harrison, he can
include the exclusion in the prevention
rule, do you mean adding another rule, a
nested role or something like that? No,
no. So go now you have it on block, so
go to that next tab setting. So here you
would add a row. And yeah,
just, yeah, do select field or yeah, if
you can build a condition like if you
have all the users and like a condition,
you can use that. But just cancel out of
here for a moment. Let me just show you
what I mean. So yeah, select field here
and just go to user and then just go
to username. Right. We're we're not going
to save this. You would do username or
group name, whatever you want to fill in
there is not right. So anyone who's in
this group will basically will not get
the Yeah, not in right now. This will
exclude these users from this DLP rule
processing, right. That's pretty much
what I was, Yeah. OK.
Yes, you could do username, you could do
group name with. Well, you guys don't
have the AD sync set up just yet, but
yeah, eventually when that's all said and
done, you can use an AD group. You can
use an individual user name, or if you
want to build a condition with the names,
you could do it that way as well. All
three of them should work.
I think I mentioned this last time, just
something that, you know, kind of be
conscious of for the AD sync is that it
will only happen once every 24 hours. So
yeah, just just keep that in mind. If
you're adding users to a group that's
going to be referenced in a rule, it
won't take effect like right away, right?
It will only sync. Group membership once
a day Now, um, there have been
instances where we've increased the
sinking frequency for customers, so we
can talk about that if it ends
up being necessary. But yeah, by default
it's just once a day.
What what happened if the sync fail still
runs with the previous sync? Yeah or
yeah. Yeah, Perfect. Yeah, I remember
talking about it and it being our
preference would be actually reducing the
time. We just need to figure it out.
But what's the sweet spot? OK, perfect.
Ryan, are you OK with the question?
You're good. I'm good for now. So yes,
thank you so much. That was helpful.
Yeah, absolutely. Yeah. Ryan, just I
don't know if you've been on the calls
recently. This might be a first time
meeting. Yeah, first time. OK. Well, you
have my info from the from the invite
details. So if anything else comes up.
Yeah, I've been mostly working on the
DSM side. And so I since I
wasn't quite sure how to test with
DPM yet, I was also tagging the
endpoint channel so that I could sort
of test through endpoint. But I haven't
been making endpoint roles. I've mostly
been focusing on detectors and rules.
Trying to get everything ready for TSM.
Got it, Got it. OK, it's good to
meet you. Which is a good segue. How
are you finding me?
Harris that was sorry, let's go back to
chat because he had a question. Maybe
he's writing before we jump into our
chat. You're ready for your question or?
No, I think I'm actually OK. I'm
reviewing the doc and I don't have
anything. GPS DLP or
ITM right now that's jumping out
um. Yeah. All right, go ahead.
Sorry. Thank you. Yeah, No, we were
talking about this in a previous call,
but wanted to bring it to you, Harris.
And so Ryan was mentioning like so in
the endpoint portal, we make the
detectors there and there's a flag for
always on in DSM and then.
Those detectives would then be
automatically being used as scans
of running against the data
stores configured there. So we
are having. We've done that,
but we're not able to
see in DSM the.
Those detectors shoring up in the
results if Hagar did allude to
some type of the detectors don't
show up in DSM, but there
might be work going on about
that, but it was a little
bit unclear. So that's you know.
We're trying to, we realize we can't go
into GPM to create our detectors there.
We're supposed to make them in the
endpoint portal and they're leveraged by
DPN on that side. But we're seeing a bit
of a disconnect. So we're hoping you
could shed some light on that, if that
makes sense. So you have the specific
detectors. To evaluate DPM always and
then what's happening on the DPM
side. So Howard has some data
storage configured and when we look
at whatever type results that are
presented, we're seeing more of the
out-of-the-box that NZ.
Out-of-the-box signatures and classifiers
and not our classifiers
that we created in
the endpoint site that
are already slacked to
always evaluate and DSM.
OK, Howard, do you have it up or one of
us can log in and like, yeah, go ahead
and share with your hand. Yeah, yeah, let
me log in because I don't have it open at
the moment in a second, not the case
number. If you have a question, be
prepared to share.
And secondly. Learning by
getting into the fire.
So you just Scroll down. These are in
there so well we believe right now. Is
that for whatever reason whatever
whispered of authenticator like we don't
have that many customers on our side,
right that would push through this again,
we have the feeling that whatever we're
setting up in our size, you know, being
reflected on on the data that's being
scanned, correct. That's how we're
assumption right now, OK.
Is there one really generic one that you
guys can turn on that we can just
test?
Or should these be firing already like
the ones that you guys have set up the
detectors, the custom ones, this should
be firing already, right? Look, I tried
to go on the VPN site and click on
update the help settings. I do that at
least once a week, right?
Yeah, everything that seems to
be coming up is the
out-of-the-box the FBM detectors.
OK. Uh, can you open the DSM side? Yeah,
I'm going to do both because I just want
to show you, OK.
Yeah, this.
One second.
That was going to show you the detector
stuff with the flags, but it sounds like
you trust so. Just
here.
See.
OK. And where do you want to go?
On the left panel is they're like,
yeah. So go to scan config and
then they're detector here, no.
Um would are you and it will be an
entity. It's not showing there will be an
entity. So if you click on entities.
This is all these out-of-the-box
NZ. These are all just
normalize their stuff out-of-the-box
stuff. I'm sorry, got page
2 so you can.
See. So we also
have to create them
here. No, no we
don't. But they
should show here somehow, apparently
related to fly. So if what was the other
section that had told us to go, Yeah,
remember now he said that it should be.
Like detectors. What you said, Harris,
you said detectors should be an
option here. Yeah, because that's what
I'm also seeing underscan fix. Can
you?Is there, um, are
you like a fool? You have like full
permissions on here? I don't think so.
Howard, do you have purple functions on
here? Yeah, No, no, you do have
permissions, yes.
So. Hmm.
Are you running a different somehow
version than than than us?
Umm, I don't actually have access to
this DSM tool because this tool, but
I'm just looking based on the
documentation we have on how to manage
the detectors and the data classes and
it's showing in the left panel. If
you go to scan config there should
be a detectors tab.
So if you just go Yep, Yep, you see
all the way at the bottom here at the
bottom of this document you have open.
OK, you see how it says, yeah, go all
the way to the bottom? Yeah, right there.
So Scroll down a little bit. Yeah, you
see in the left panel down config
detectors. Yeah, like,
like, you see that, right? There's no,
yeah, this is July of 2026. This was
updated. So I mean, this was this month.
Do we know if what's being advertised
to us is like, uh.
Because there is a later version than
this than this platform.
Uh, I can double OK, I I
would have to ask around just because
I don't support this tool necessarily, so
I'm really not in here much.
But from my understanding, you should be
able to leverage those same data classes.
Howard, when you open this, you you're
you're an admin on the Cloud Console,
the DSP console as well, right? Yeah,
I don't have that option. And but
my understanding from the previous call
is that there's. You were version of
this interface that takes away all these
NC values and we only uses the
stuff that we have on the DSP
side, right? However don't if you
actually go into the data store section
OK, one second. Actually
gone to the data store and we see things
that we scan. Apparently the Sumption is
that we should be able to. You will need
to click on the on the thing. Yeah, click
on Leo. You know what I think?
I think that detector option is a
limited release right now and we might
have to turn it on for you.
OK, so that so then it's probably
not turned on for your tenant if
you guys don't see it here, Yeah,
click apply it applies. That's yeah. And
just see right here. Data, and this is
where we should be able to find this
stuff that triggers our beta. And if you
we actually search for any of those
detectors that we're actually pushing
here because yeah, so click on entities,
data, entities in the middle. No, no, no,
in the middle section.
And then click on this. Yeah, look for
one of these detectors and you see no
results. Every. Yeah, I see, I see the
detectors as a limited release that's
available for select customers right now.
So yeah, that was actually a new feature
in DPM where the detector release. So
it's probably something that we need to
turn on for you. Since it's an IGA.
Um, so would it be safe to assume
that everything that we scan it right now
is only running on the out-of-the-box
DSPE detectors? That I don't want to give
you the wrong answer because again, I
don't necessarily work on the DPM side,
but from what I'm looking at, yeah,
that's what it looks like.
Um. Yeah, I'm looking now
that there's a limited release. So yeah,
we need to put in a request to actually
get this toggle into your tenant.
So yeah, I guess Tim, if you want to
uh, are you selling here, Tim? Yeah, we
can connect on it afterwards. Either I
can like open a ticket for them or you
can have are they working with Haga for
DSM, Right, Yeah, Yeah. So I'm sorry
because I was just.
Are we back to that original question we
had about setting up a, an inquiry or is
it we have so, so basically there's a
feature they need to have exposed on
their tenants. So what connect offline?
But I think Howard, it's just, it's
something that we need to switch on from.
From what I'm seeing, it looks like it's
just like limited release right now. Ohh,
OK, so yeah, pig with the with a little
maybe he can enable it. If not, maybe not
provision, but with that's on us to to
provide that. So yeah, Howard, we'll,
we'll get that sorted out. I'll I'll
shoot a message to Hago and and and we'll
figure it out. But it looks like it's
just a toggle that needs to be turned on
so that. Functionality can be enabled.
Someday I'll pronounce our group's name
correctly too, because every day I I do
it, I have to ask him. He does. He's
so gentlemanly about, you know, like he
doesn't. He never corrects me. But thank
you for that. Yeah, I'll. I'll connect
with. I'm meeting with him in a little
while anyway, so just ping them. Been on
teams and we can come back here
with an update ASAP. Yeah, thank you.
We'll keep you posted, Howard and team.
Or so from from what I'm seeing that that
should that should take care of it then
you should be able to use the DSP
detectors and ESPN. So that should be
good.
OK. So don't you're OK with that
question, with that, would that answer
you're good. Yes, sounds good. Like we
just need that flag turned on. So I'm
glad you brought it up and it's known
that it needs to be turned on. So
yeah, right now. OK, perfect.
So another question, this is kind of
tight up to the call that we
had yesterday, um. The documentation for
the new API, is that something that is
available or when can we get access to
it?
Um, Marina, you want to take that one
down? Yeah, I sent you a link. But
in the past for David, every API we'll
probably follow up with another session,
but it's part of the dev tools. I
mean, we send out them to you. OK,
so that that API really. Yeah, we're
still in the works because my
understanding is near right. So I wasn't
sure if it's something that is already
exposed to everybody was just with the IT
is available according to what promises
mentioned. We actually have customers
actively using it. So I'm going to.
You'll probably want to have follow on
questions once you look at the
documentation. So we'll probably have
that with our session with that.
Perfect.
Alright, uh, do you think any questions
from my end?
Goodbye. I
have a question. I should be
good. Thank you very much. Yeah.
So this is to do with
the ITM rules switching the screen
quickly.
Uh.
OK.
Can you see my screen?
Yes, OK, so we created
a bunch of ITM.
And we're all similar to what we
have to the under on Prem solution
today and using the trick lively. So
we just save as and edit to
fit what we're trying to achieve. And
we have about 55 of those rules
right now set up.
Um. In
order to get those rules to
um. Written
alert or just generate incidents.
Umm, we have we have.
Um. It's in
policy which is the dev
ITM test and I think
it was signed.
You can edit this under General and then
it'll show up here. That's it
right there. So he's gonna details up
there. Is there US specific users in
there or is it?
Right here. Yeah, I did this and then go
to details at the top. Details. Yeah. So
I signed it to myself because I'm trying
to do some testing.
Quick quick, quick question here. Why
is the file activity monitoring turned
off?
Umm, because that needs to be turned
on and it's been able to put
for it. Yeah,
it doesn't. OK, so maybe that's why my
rules are not fine.
That's not happening any file activities.
So OK, so have you couple of
tests and I haven't seen any.
Um, but that's been generated to do it
ATM. Just wanted to confirm that we're
doing it the right way to ensure that we
can get. Um, some
because I'm trying to do some
testing my test video, I'm showing
sure that we have complicated policies
the right way and then we
can start seeing some alerts on
the dashboard. So I think that's
probably what the problem is.
Well, for file related rule file activity
related rules, yeah, you wouldn't see
them without turning that on. But if you
have some rules are not fair listed as
well. But I still haven't seen any
activity. So let's can we just walk
through? Yeah, let's go through one of
the rules and then you can test it and
let's see what's happening. OK, so if we
go to. While you're pulling that up,
um, Howard and Dom, I just messaged hug
up on the side and he did, he
did mention that he submitted the request
already like an hour ago. So you guys
should be good.
So many times people would
be. Umm.
PowerShell Windows terminal users, does
that require fire monitoring anymore? No,
no, no. So can you go to the right and
Scroll down? I just want to see exactly
is this window title contains or
something? Yeah. Just go
down, go down here. So
click OK, So user click
on that information bubble next
to the second condition next
to the word usage, Yeah.
OK. All right. So you open PowerShell
and you're in, I assume you're this,
you're in that group there, right? Yep.
OK. OK, yeah.
So this should be fine. Um.
Yeah, go down here 0 activities. Alright,
so do you want to?
Can you open it right now and let's see
what's going on? Sure.
Welcome to my YEAH.
Ohh.
OK.
5 minutes.
Yes, that's for sure. OK,
open up. So if we go
to. Yeah, open
the workbench and then just run
an exploration for your own user.
Exactly.
So let me see
2105.
OK, so. Uh,
yeah, it's not sure just yet.
Um, just refresh there. You can
refresh on the right here, then
you won't lose the filter.
OK.
Can you throw some like command
in there OK or something like
that?
Umm.
22222.
So I'm still
checking updates.
OK, yeah. And now maybe go back and see
once you've interacted with it, if it's
picking up now, because you should
actually see a command line.
What is?
OK, yeah, that's this is what I just did,
but I just closed. I was kind of on the
PowerShell, just taking some time to load
up the picture.
Because remember I searched for
PowerShell and then launched but.
OK.
Can you do me a favor and add um?
Like in this area right here
and you just add the activity
category here.
Ohh sorry, you see my drawing here? Umm
hold on a second, let me just.
OK, Yeah, yeah, yeah. And then
just add the under activity, just
click on categories, the first one.
And then just hit done.
OK, go down here. I
just want to see if
we see any command execution.
Click on this one.
So this was July 6.
Yeah, I did that on
Monday. Same.
Open the travel show, but.
It wasn't tagged as the ITM.
But.
Umm.
But we remember we only have one license
for ATM. So it's just the thing has to
do with licensing or is it? No, I mean,
well, either way. I mean you're the only
one assigned in the IPM, right? So yeah,
it should. I mean, either way it should
still pick it up. I'm wondering why it's
not seeing those command. Executions
right now.
Hey how does citizen option in
the agent room settings for it
to?Truncate
the terminology of something. You want to
check that that's enabled or something?
Yeah, I know because that's a fairly new
option. I'm just wondering if that might
be something to do with this. OK, yeah,
let's take advantage. Take a look.
So agent room, right?
Options No Do edit
and then advanced options.
You're going to settings. Shiki,
where is it in here? You know
what it's called? Uh, yeah. Just control
us and do terminal.
Uh.
There should be 1 uh, Scroll down.
I haven't seen that one that's checking
our lab tenant as well and I don't see
that terminal option. What would it be
under? Would it be it wouldn't be under
content stand, it would be under
processing probably. Yes. So that means
that I have seen it in my bag. Let me
pull that up. What makes it OK?
Can you just leave this open? Is that
separate? Is the other tab proof when you
have open the exploration or or did you
open?Ohh yeah, OK yeah, just open the
workbench again and I just want to see.
Yeah, I want to see, yeah, open a
new exploration and drew your name and
then do another filter for application
name. And then I just want to see
if we're seeing PowerShell at all in
there. Here's one name.
Name and she gave us a letter. Know if
you see it in there. I just want to check
this out. 21011
and then add a new
filter here our new filter
hold on there it is
346 command execution. OK, so
go down here to details.
Is it showing how is
it showing PowerShell is that?
So yeah, go down here.
And ohh, actually can you go up and
click all fields instead of just the
summary table? Yeah, details there.
And then do all fields all set at most
common fields.
OK, OK, this is the OPI
TN dot OK go down here.
And then there should be like, yeah,
process application. What is it showing
here? Windows Terminal? Yeah, is Windows
Terminal is in that condition, right?
Yes, yeah, there it is. Can we,
can we, can we check that? Because
I saw PowerShell in there. OK, let's
just double check. That rule and make
sure that it actually has this in
there. OK, Yeah, yeah, perfect.
Hmm. Um,
yeah, so it'll be
in the policies down
here, policies worlds, yes.
And then.
Yeah. So click on this and then you go
down, Scroll down and click on that eye
next to the word usage.
PowerShell, Windows 10. OK, yeah, Windows
Server is there.
Uh.
So we should be tagging this as a.
Yeah. So can you go? I wanna see if this
generated an alert. I don't think it did,
but if you go to alerts over here, yeah,
let's just see if anything I've everread.
Uh, no, it doesn't. Yeah,
OK.
Hmm.
Can you can you try editing that
rule really quickly? I just is it
OK if you make a change to
it? Hey, this is Dave. So she's
fine. OK, so I just want to
make a change and just remove the
remove the user condition. Out of there.
And yeah, so just edit that rule and I'll
show you what to do.
Yeah, yeah. So, so just yeah,
if you if you go over
here, you can just delete this
whole row. So like that, delete,
delete that and delete this one
as well. OK,
this one, Yeah, delete this and
now go to. Yeah, add a
new. Add a new row here.
And Yep, select field and then do
the same thing application name.
Oh, oh, not, not, not a condition,
not a condition. So if you go
to select field, OK, let's see if
we individually call out those processes
if we if we get under process
application here.
And then select values here and go
here. You should see them and observed.
You shouldn't have to type them all
out windows terminal so. Do
that. Yeah, Right. Yeah, yeah, yeah. And
then click done. And now. Yeah. Alright,
hold on. And yeah, yeah. There we
go. OK, so now we should generate
an alert every time we see the
Windows terminal get opened. Now go down
here. You see how it's. Already returning
our results, so click on that. Yeah,
we're. So I wonder if there's something
like on the condition that's just not
going to.
And these are, well, actually, yeah,
these are all from right now. Yeah. Yeah,
they're hard.
See it? It's when you actually hit
the command. For some reason we're not
picking up the application name. It's
only when you open the application, so.
It's a little odd.
So what I would do, because, um, you
won't really need to edit that specific
rule or those process names too much. I
would just try and I'll take it back
to see if there's something up with that
condition. Yeah, I have seen in the
past where like the condition just isn't
working as expected. And when you call
them out, um, like kind of those
applications individually, then it seems
to work. So that might be what's going on
here. I'm not entirely sure, but.
Yeah, if you want to now, if you
want to, now open that again and let's
see if it actually generates an alert for
us, because this is just showing us
activities. We still haven't seen an
alert get generated. So maybe close it.
Yeah.
OK, that should
be enough.
And I'll go to the alerts page here on
the left.
Yeah, there it is. Yeah. OK. So there
might be something up with that, with
that condition. I'll double check for
you, but it looks like it is working. So
what I would do is I would go back to
that condition and I can. But right now,
if you want to open the rule, I'll tell
you the other names, I'll just put them
in the chat and you can add them in their
custom. What does this mean
we have to do this for? Like I
said, we've created a bunch of rules
using the thread library. Doesn't mean we
have to change every single condition. I
don't think no, no, I don't think you'll
need to change every condition.
You shouldn't have to. At least the
threat library rule should be tested
already. So I know with some of them like
I have seen that. So yeah, let's go
through. Let's let's edit this rule 1st
and then and then we can go, we can
go down to the next one.
Um, ohh, God. OK, how do we I don't
think that was actually a saved
condition. Was it a was that an
out-of-the-box? Yeah, that was a threat
library. Yeah, yeah. And then we just, we
just made it into the rule. OK, let me
just open that and see exactly what's in
there.
OK, so.
So that was the rule that you
were using? Was it running command line
shell programs? Which one was it exactly?
It was. It's
under a definition there on the left it
was. Which
was PowerShell slash windows terminal
usage. So if we go to
yeah under death again.
See that in here.
Umm.
Like I see one in here that's running
command command line shell pro. OK, I
think I know what the problem is. OK,
this was created by someone. OK, let's
get it for me. Get it by mail.
OK, that's probably why one of the ITM
mails with ATM. I think he probably
created one and maybe he didn't do it
properly. That's why he didn't. It's not
fair. OK, yeah, sure. But maybe that's
what. Yeah, yeah. That wasn't actually
that you had set up was not a threat
library rule. There is a threat library
rule that shows. It
might be interesting to you if you want
to take a look, but if you go to the
threat library and put running command or
just put running.
Yeah, you should see.
Yeah, the last one running command line
shell program. So this will have I mean
this this obviously has terminal and
PowerShell and stuff in it as well. But
if you look at if you click on this
eye here, this is a much more
comprehensive list, I would say. OK,
yeah, so maybe he probably didn't. He
made him. But you just made an error
with the typing in the application name.
Yeah, OK, Yeah, but let's go through one
of the other rules. I mean, you can
now, you see, so you can go in
and add those. I mean, that's not their
library rule, so you'll have to customize
it. Can you show me one of the?
The ones that use that up from
the threat library, that's this one
process cracking activity. This one
search use search is predefined keywords.
So if we look at condition says
any kind of search for hold on.
So this one is called running password
or license. OK. All right,
Now listen, hold on a second. Let me
say, is this what you're showing me? This
is not a. Who's
gonna rule No no. OK, hold on
a second. There is one that's running
a password or license cracking tool so
that will detect when a user runs
one of the predefined like. License
cracking tools.
Just find one. Yeah, these are
these are custom that he made.
Like opening tour I think that one
is.
I they're running core browser, I saw
that in there that is a threat library
rule. I don't know if you have access
problems that we don't have access so.
OK OK this one says
searching for data on dynamic
DNS. So this is one
of the.
Rule 1 of the rules that yeah, this
is OK so this one says search for
if you searching for any of these you
should fire right just click on that Let
me see so this is saying if you're
web browsing and the URL domain contains
any of these search. Engines
and.
The URL also contains DNS
window time. Yeah.
OK. So can you, are you able
to just say if I go to?
Search engine right? And I type in.
DD clients.
Alright, go to the client
through.
This should fire, right?
Yeah, it should.
The URL, yeah, it's using the contained
statements. So it's saying if the URL
contains one of those keywords or the
window title contains some of those
keywords. So I mean really on either one
of them it should work. OK, so if
we go to. And it
works.
Let's.
Umm.
So this fire, but fire is under a
different rule.
OK. Can you look at the top one?
You Scroll down on the right. Is it
firing on any other rule? Uh, let me
see.
So yeah, Scroll down. It probably hit
this DLP rule and then didn't process,
didn't process the other one. OK, that's
really what it is. Go down. Is there?
Yeah, go to rules, Yeah. So it's probably
just that one.
But actually it should
still show over here.
I wonder if it
matches the condition of
the itsi monitored users,
which is me.
There's nothing else.
Shortcuts.
Give me a SEC.
All of the commands and
coming from OK.
Turn it up. Yeah.
OK. Yeah. So it is going to
actually, um, can we just look at
the order of those rules? I just
want to confirm like where the placement
is because I think what it's doing
is it's evaluating them top down in
the order they're listed here, so.
Under, under policies and then,
yeah. And OK, and
then what you'll need to do is Scroll
down here. Um, we'll need to so find that
the rule that was called out, the DLP
rule and that alert, what was it called
exactly?That one
is you can find out that's
a policy. Yeah,
that's, yeah, you're in the right spot.
This this little thing here? Yeah. Do you
remember that? The name? You might have
it open on that other tab still. I
don't know if I don't think so. Let
me just go back to, you know.
And.
So it's called the proud
enhance the API enhancements. OK,
this one alright.
And now if you just go down here,
you don't need to search it, just go
down and see where that rule is. So
it should be DLP.
Well, um.
I think that falls
under um.
And that's boards, yes, yeah, Asian
policy, it's a prevention, it's a
prevention rule. It's a prevention rule.
So enhance, I think it's one of
these ones, this one I don't, I
don't think so only because we didn't
get any end user notification, right,
which we would have. If it was
like a block or prompt you would have
seen something pop up on your screen. OK,
so you think it's under the?
Uh. Policies
or let me see if
I can find it in
here. Yeah, there
it is. There is this one.
Hey Shakib, so I know I'm
the prevention rules. The first match
behavior is basically applied for the
detection rules, um. We should actually
evaluate independently, right? So single
activity should that alert pane should
show us multiple detection rules if it
hit. Yes, yeah. OK.
So I actually should be hitting both.
All right, go back to the exploration and
look at your look at your activity again
and let's see what we are seeing here.
You have that? OK, this is the looks. Did
you want to go through? Yeah, you could
just click on new exploration here.
All right. Is is that?
You can also just click on your name over
here if you see it. OK,
well let's let's run over here now.
Yeah, you could just click enter, like
add it. Yeah, OK, yeah.
OK, so um, website open Google. Alright,
so click on that, click on the
first one. That was the one that
we were looking at so.
I said. If
the URL domain contains good, yeah, I
mean yours has Google on here.
Um, go all the way down, yeah, details.
And then go all the way down here to
rules.
Yeah, click on that indicator
tab and click.
What was your Yeah, so
it only hit the DP
rule. Go to the alert
section, Office alert section, Yeah,
just above.
Yeah, it only hit on this rule.
So this is not the rule that
it, I mean it may have, you
know, this may also capture this, but
it should show our additional rule around
like the DNS. Yeah, exactly.
Yeah, it it usually in detection it
should show multiple rules. Uh, doesn't
matter. So if you go Scroll down
to the bottom, you'll see anything in
the context part like.
Contacts. Contacts,
yeah.
Can you click on event?
Yeah, that's correct.
This one.
Yeah. I don't see
any errors on the agency there either.
We need to see if it's so so was
it? Was it right away when it mattered?
Then tested with this activity. It's
like, was it what did you make any
changes to the rule right now or no, no,
we just we just tested. We didn't make
any change. So, so let me. Ask you this,
should you go back to the rule? Um, just
in the spirit of cleaning up some of the
rules, I wonder if it would make sense
to. Yeah,
let me let me show you something here. So
yeah, go to that rule.
Umm.
Yeah, click on this so.
And then edit the second
box conditions and actions. So
would we even need really?
Well, I guess you can keep the monitored
users, but. Ohh,
wait, can you expand these down
a little bit? Which ones? Yeah,
right, right here. Ohh. Sorry. This
one. OK.
So I don't know that these really matter,
right? I mean, if you click on this,
this should be enough. Right click on
this eye and you'll see it. This is
just the window title. The URL contains
these or the window title contains these.
This should be more than enough for the
rule. I don't know if you even need.
Like the rest of the attributes in there.
So why does the rules, why does
the trend line we have that as
part of the let me just see
here maybe modified. I don't think so,
just check searching data dynamic DNS.
Because the trend might be will has
that as well. So we didn't make
any changes, we just saved as.
If you Scroll down to the rule does it
when it under test condition does it show
any activities?They
just can't only be the. Yeah,
because I think the the predicates
here are pretty complicated. How many
contains filters have you used? Things
Scroll up, scroll up here. Yeah,
just the logic.
OK, uh, can you hover over
the?This, this
one. Which one? The exclamation
mark in the second condition.
This, this one. This one,
Yeah.
OK.
This is complicated.
Ohh.
Yeah, we need, we need to test this
happens offline because I have seen a
couple of thread library logics not not
me not working actually. Yeah, that was
going to be my yeah. And I've seen
that as well. Kind of why I changed
the initial 1 is that there have been
instances where these. Threat library
rules are not working
as expected, um. So
yeah, we can help you go through and like
sort of customize these. But from my
perspective, right, I mean, this
condition should be enough ideally,
right? We're just saying if the, if the
window title contains these keywords or
the URL contains these keywords, these to
me are a little bit redundant.
So, because this is what I'm thinking,
right, and you can correct me if I'm
wrong, is that it needs to see the
web browsing and then all of these,
right? And so, I mean, ideally it should
kind of work, but like you said, there's
so many predicates in here. Yeah, maybe
it has to. So technically it has to.
Kids and also these together
and then it can choose
between this one or this
one to trigger. So that's
a lot of predicates, right?
I think we can simplify
this if we know the
use case exactly.
Yeah, I think it would. It would just
be like the user condition and then this
condition that should be more than enough
to trigger what you guys needed to
trigger. OK, OK, I'll, I'll look for the
rules and see, continue to test and see
which ones I can clean up.
Based on what you just said and I just
don't want to take up the rest of the 15
minutes left. So I'll get back to you if
I have any additional questions about
that. And but we just kind of touch them
as much as possible. Yeah, there is,
there is one that I'm aware of that I
also do you guys have the opening proof
point agent folder rule?Set up.
No, no, I don't think we do. No, we
don't. But that one, there's that one,
that one. I know that.
That the yeah, if you open it, I I wanna
see if they updated it. So yeah click on
this and then go down resource URL
content Yeah so this one.
This one I haven't seen work like
properly using the resource URL. For some
reason this field is just not firing in
this world the way it needs to be. So I
actually just fix this rule with another
customer. So this one would need to be so
if you click go up here.
And save as a rule. For example, you
don't have to fully save it, but what
you would change is you would add window
title contains these instead of resource
URL and then it works OK. So it
should be windows side and then you
should be window title content. OK, I'll
search for that. I'll try to go through
and see if there's other ones that like
I've seen in the past, like I know this
opening um. Um.
We're opening the proof point agent
folder. That one was one that I saw
right, that that I just recently had to
fix. But yeah, let us know if there's
other. Yeah. Which is which is why we
wanted to have the session with the ATM
exclusively for the ATM rules. What we're
still working through creating all the
rules. Once we're done, I'll reach out to
Timothy to have. That session.
Scheduled so we can have, we can go to
all the rules and then clean them up as
much as possible. Yep. Alright, thank
you. That's all for me.
Yeah, that was an hour. Sorry. Yeah,
I know. Where is this guy? Sorry
about that. Alright, so anybody else have
a question or I can go with
mine.
Perfect, let me share my screen and
hopefully you guys can help me with this
so.
OK. So couple of
questions. Is
there any way to actually
have access so integrated into
this back end URLs?
Or or or how did you
guys was expectation to protect this
this year?
You should talk to Daniel if I don't
know if he's confused yet. Under system
side, on the system menu, just Scroll
down on the left hand side. Yeah, yeah,
yeah. User off, import off profiles.
OK. Yeah, he hasn't added it yet,
but I thought he configured it for
the Yeah, click on add and then
he could set best himself. So the
SSO for this profile is for this
console is different than for for the
data security platform. Yeah. And then?
He could define it. I thought they had
approval to do this. Um, unless he might
not have got around to configure it and,
and for this for this pod. OK, yeah.
And I, I'm not sure if he's going
to be doing this because technically we
are responsible for this pause. So most
likely. Has to be announced to
make this happen. OK, so I
would basically come here and go
into like a SAML and then
go through the setup.
Yeah, I'll give you the documentation,
but like I said it up, Yeah.
And then all the details that you
need to configure. OK, perfect. Yeah,
this got me worried this morning a
little bit, but I guess this answers
that question. Chad, do you need a
screen shot from here?I'm taking some.
The anyway DPS
e-mail appliances, right?
Yes, correct, correct.
Here we go. Let me just move this a
little bit so you see the option. So it
will be an important profile and it's out
of here. Yeah, so. Yeah,
but ohh wait consumer URL.
So it looks like the
URLs are.
Hmm, that's interesting.
It will have to submit a request to the
entry ID team on our side to get the
SSO and I'm wondering if it has to be
per device if the consumer URL has the
device identifier in it. Seems to be the
case. We'll see. I don't know exactly how
that works, Hopefully not right?
Hopefully you can reuse the same one for
all. Of devices, but at least we know
now it has Samuel too. So that's good.
Yeah. So, so now that's actually a good
question. We're going to have three
devices at least from production
understanding is 1 is going to be 4,
the user relay, one for app relay and
then another one potentially for UMP
relay. Like can we reduce the same as
so or they have to be stored
independently based on this parameter?
I I don't believe you can reuse it
um. I mean, I guess you could with
the certificate of. That might be a
question for. Daniel
had our Daniel on saying that.
I might I'll need to come back to you on
that, but I. I don't think
he could really use it, but let me let me
get back to you could also check on it
with our on our side. Howard would like
when we submit the ticket for the one I
guess right and see what the Android team
says. Yeah,
well, The Who? Who on our side would be
working on this?
So I think it's going to be a guy
called Harry from the WIN team. He's the
one that set it up for.
For the other stuff they, sorry, I meant
like who's gonna submit the ticket to
engage? Ohh yeah, that's a good question.
And he might be Fernando or more or
Evan. I I'm not
sure OK if I could try. I don't know I
don't have the link but I could I could
give it a try. To
that page and submitted child.
OK, I do have the link. I can send you
the link too. Yeah, I got the link. OK.
That way at least I know who to talk to
you on our side. So. Right. Perfect.
Thank you, Mike. Appreciate it. Yeah, no
problem. OK, so that
was one of the questions about this. Um,
what about, what about the roles just
while we're here, like assigning that.
OK, now you got S so how do
you assign what that user can do?
I don't think that dynamic access is,
yeah. So what happens is you sign
in with your e-mail address and then
based on your e-mail address you'd be
putting it, it would link to account
that's provisioned. In the console and
then in there you would be able to assign
the role. So when he created an admin
user, you'll put in the admin user's
e-mail address and then you'd be able to
assign the role. So if you go on our
administration. And yeah,
so you have that then. So you
create the user first, you put the
appropriate e-mail, the SSO validates
that they are who they are by
their e-mail basically. And then that's
how they get their role. OK, Yeah,
yeah. Being charged
the question was so that that's actually
on the admin on this side right
But I most likely the guy that
you're working with he might also
question this right. There's no
granularity here. You can see how this
adequacy yeah quarantine are these static
or concussion. You could add additional
roles, just add button there and then you
could disable certain things like for
example like Daniel on your team would
want to just do smart search and nothing
else. You would create a role for like
the messaging team. I don't know if the
messaging team would also. I used to. I
was hoping that they would assume
responsibility for the intra integration.
You can also give them access to
like specific modules or specific or you
might have access and nothing else and
then you may have different
administrators that.
At a very, I don't think there'll be many
much use to log into this console,
Howard, only on certain edge use cases.
Most of it will be in the more modern
console. But you would you would, you
would be able to define these roles and
then you would be able to once they're
defined and when you go to the admin
administrator, you could assign that role
to that administrator.
Yeah, we're getting grilled on rolls and
capability mapping right now as part of
like the the plan. So before we're even
allowed to go to prod, they're they're
wanting to see like who will have what
access in each of the different tooling.
So we're just kind of collecting that
view. Yeah. OK. So this is
how granular it could be, Chad.
And if you want to do a screen share
for an example for, yeah, I'll take it.
But you know, it's good to know, but it's
not really. Yeah, tell us who has what at
the end, but at least this idea.
OK, OK ohh yeah, I agree with this for
now. I'll start playing around later. OK
perfect. Yeah I think we need to move
people away for now and just give me like
a criminal this stuff like I probably
don't want ever guys to tell looking at
the at the routing and stuff
configuration. OK, perfect. So
I think I don't have anything else on the
side chat. Do you have any questions
around the appliance? This this guy here,
are you good? No, sounds good. Sounds
like another stuff. So I'll update the
document for that. That's good. Perfect.
Actually, I do have one more question. So
when it comes to groups. Right. I noticed
that I can actually see some growth that
somehow got imported here. Um, when we
start adding groups to our e-mail
policies right at those groups are going
to show here in the back end as
well or. Consideration for import
all profiles, you'll be able to do an
intro ID import. So I will
have to go also here in trade import.
Yeah, OK. And how that can you tell me
like it just high level how that actually
works?So we'll have
to integration. Yeah. And then you would
you would set up and then then if
you need to do anything custom under the
advanced tab, you you would be able to
like change the mappings. But it's it's
pretty straightforward. It should be
pretty much identical to what you have on
the Seagate. Yeah.
But I'll, I'll provide you with that.
Yeah, we, we can go through the setup,
OK? Because I think Raghu had a concern
about what was actually being pushed to
you guys, right. And he had some
questions. It was just a scheme, right?
So I might need to touch base with you
offline to see what exactly is Bush and
what you guys will have. Actually, you
know what this platform will have access
once it's set up, right, when it will
sync. Now I'll be in the documentation in
terms of what we need in terms of our
service account. Yeah. So
I'll, I'll document, I'll send it over
and if there's something missing, yeah, I
can provide it. OK, perfect. Thank you.
Appreciate it. And I know we only have a
few more minutes, so just a couple of
quick questions more when I'm going over
the search functionality and just because
I run a lot of tests, right, I haven't
been able to. Find a way where I can
actually say OK show me everything and
exclude this guy here. For example, is
there any way to actually have a filter
that says you know exclude different
recipient or sender? So if it goes
envelope sender and I want to say it's
not this guy. That's
that's a good feature request. Now
there's there's not that you yeah, you
should submit that. I do agree that
that use case comes up occasionally.
Yeah, I'm surprised. Question should be
all the time because you have to
basically go and take scrolling down and
you know. Was
in production, it kind of gets drowned
out, but yeah, like right now in the lab
environment is kind of annoying because
you only seeing a couple of messages in
an hour. Yeah, yeah. OK. So
the the answer to that is not yet. We
need our RFP, OK. But
the other one is just a request. I don't
have this information, but if you have
the the URLs for the plug URL for the
app relay and the UMP relay for the DLP
boxes, if you have those and you could
send them to me that would be great. I
could check with Dan about himself for.
He isn't training so I would need to wear
the next week, but I'm trying to see if
we can get the application policies up
and running this week. It's only a few of
them, so I would like to get that out of
my pocket. OK, I was on a call with them
earlier. What about Jet jet around?
Uh, I don't know, but I don't
know if they have this information right
because nobody because they're also need
to create an account for you. So
if not them on your own.
Uh, until we had our own code admin
for those boxes, because remember, I'm,
I'm not referring to the the the second
talking about just the the specific plot
for you for the help. Alright, yeah,
well, happen is they'll it'll be just the
cloud admin interface. They need to
create an account for you. Cloud Admin
interface you will need. You will need to
have access to the pod, the classic
interface because you'll be only doing
the configuration through the. Uh,
the if there's a use case for
an e-mail firewall or information
protection, everything else that they
would be administrating. So it
would be just so they modified it. Yeah,
yeah. So what if I need to create a
domain set? They won't be able to. I will
have to create that myself, right? Yeah.
Then what they can do is they can give
you role based access so you can create
domain set.
Dean, that's the place. That's a pause.
That's a pause. That's a good place to
call it a day. We're we're a minute
overdue. But is there anything NAV or
team, anything too close that must be
addressed right now or can it wait till
Friday?No, I
still have some follow up about this, but
it can work. It certainly Sir. And I know
we have homework. We have some things
going on on on site, you know, side
threads, but we're working towards that.
I'll get with Dave Reese on some other
things that were raised during this call
or the earlier call and we'll get, we'll
get him tackled. Everyone have a good
evening. We'll talk again tomorrow. Thank
you. Thank you guys. I appreciate it.
Have a good day. Bye.